backcountryedge.com 2016-12-07

# Privacy Policy

## Information Collection & Use 

At Backcountry Edge, Inc. we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. Any personal information that you provide will be used strictly in accordance with the policies described below. We will not sell your personal information to any outside third parties.

#### Orders 

If you purchase a product from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email address, telephone number, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). 

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

We may occasionally send you information on products, promotions and special deals. 

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see "Choice and Opt-out." 

#### Newsletters 

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure 

#### Personally identifiable information

We use a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. We share personally identifiable information with this company. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

#### Legal Disclaimer 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

#### Choice/Opt-out 

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following one of the methods outlined below: 

1\. Follow the simple unsubscribe instructions included in each newsletter or communication.   
2\. Email your opt-out request to [privacy@backcountryedge.com](mailto:privacy@backcountryedge.com)  
3\. Mail your opt-out request to:

Backcountry Edge  
708 Ditz Drive  
Manheim, PA 17545

4\. Call our Customer Service department toll-free at 1-800-617-0643, 9AM-5:30PM EST, Monday through Friday.

Please note that even if you opt out, you may still receive non-promotional emails, such as emails about your purchases, your Inside Edge account and membership, or general information about our business relationship with you.

#### Log Files 

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

#### Cookies 

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site to match users to the contents of their shopping carts and to provide us and our service providers with information that we will use to personalize our site in accordance with your preferences.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve badges on our website and to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to our website by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). You may also opt out of third party vendor’s use of cookies for internet-based advertising by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://htwww.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

#### Links to Other Sites 

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Backcountry Edge, Inc. Please be aware that we, Backcountry Edge, Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

#### Security 

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

#### Business Transitions 

In the event Backcountry Edge, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

#### Changes in this Privacy Statement 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here. 

#### Contact Us 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [privacy@backcountryedge.com](mailto:privacy@backcountryedge.com)
